so today is Monday March 16th tomorrow
is st. Patrick's Day on Saturday a few
days ago I traveled from Vancouver to
Alberta I decided not to cancel my my
flight that I had planned from November
I decided to come in so as socially
isolate in Alberta instead of in BC
partly because we have the trip planned
for a while it cost me a lot of money it
took me a long time to say out for this
trip and also because my roommate back
in Vancouver is more medically fragile
than my mom and stepped out here so if
for some reason we do contract the virus
we're a lot less likely to pass it on to
somebody who's more medically fragile as
well as it's what's besides going
through the airport which was very dead
by the way and did having have any kind
of screening going on well me and my kid
are hacking coughing that we've been
doing for all of 2020 that's a whole
other when itself but during this time
over the last few days I've realized
that I have a lot to offer both just Who
I am on this planet and what I'm doing
and the technology cooperative and the
troops that that I'm my journey when I
have to give but also as somebody who's
had to solve isolate for a long time we
need the world to do what I've been
doing for the last few years I wasn't
doing it for contagion reasons I was
doing it for sensory reasons and mental
issues but now the world needs to do
that the world needs to be in their
house 90% of the time and with that is a
lot of emotional and financial and
interpersonal emotions and stuff that's
going to be brought up so I'm gonna
release a few videos on that on what
hopefully if anyone can get anything out
of what I've been through the last few
years I want to offer that to people
also what I am here to do in the journey
that I'm showcasing is that everyone has
something to contribute and my something
to contribute the more I step into it
and the more I let go of everything
contribute is my brain likes to create
solutions it can't actually make the
solutions I don't have the energy or
finances to pay somebody else to use
their energy to make them but I can
generate solutions between my house in
Vancouver and staying with my mom I
think I generated about a dozen I could
even tweet because we were in the air
and I can have a conversation and that
is what I've been doing before the
coronavirus hit I've been offering my
solutions to the world and what a great
time to be able to come together and
create a world that works for everyone
from love abundance and peace because we
can see what happens when we feel like
we're in LAC and we feel like we're
scared in scarcity and we want someone
else to have the answers they don't have
the answers which I think more and more
people can see clearly during this
crisis our governments are doing kind of
the best job they can and it is woefully
inadequate and so I'm gonna be really
seen several videos this week probably
because I have like 20 ideas so I'm
gonna pick top four or five it might
even release them all today because I'm
sure they'll generate new ideas but
before I did my next video which is on
my solutions raising Facebook group
which is my powerful contribution to
what we can do during the coronavirus
self-isolation period of our human
history collective human history
vacation updating the world yeah I just
wanted to update you of why there's a
different background and before I just
jump into what stew solution or his
needs on Facebook together so that is
what I am doing I am self isolating in
Edmonton instead of Vancouver now and I
am going to visit my extended family who
are also hopefully self isolating but we
won't be going out to any public events
we are not even all going out as a
family to do things like grocery
shopping we are figuring out how to best
get through this time together
and hopefully I'm able to travel back to
Vancouver
when planned at the end of March but
we'll see we'll see what how the world
is
at that period of time this is part of
what I can offer during this time of
crisis is to let go of certainty and
embrace uncertainty because life gets
easier but that will be its own series
of its own video on five lessons or ten
lessons there are many lessons I've
learned on how to get through chaos and
how do you get through social isolation
alright thank you